[
  {
    "itemName": "random_left",
    "roiFront": "17,69,132,599",
    "roiBack": "17,70,137,599",
    "description": "description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "random_right",
    "roiFront": "1133,55,131,638",
    "roiBack": "1131,55,133,638",
    "description": "description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "random_top",
    "roiFront": "84,49,1159,93",
    "roiBack": "85,46,1159,101",
    "description": "description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "random_bottom",
    "roiFront": "179,577,972,100",
    "roiBack": "179,579,972,100",
    "description": "description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "random_all",
    "roiFront": "42,94,1207,543",
    "roiBack": "42,94,1207,543",
    "description": "description"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "buff_1_up",
    "roiFront": "204,626,134,39",
    "roiBack": "204,626,134,39",
    "description": "替换buff1"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "buff_2_up",
    "roiFront": "414,625,134,39",
    "roiBack": "414,625,134,39",
    "description": "替换buff2"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "buff_3_up",
    "roiFront": "619,625,134,39",
    "roiBack": "619,625,134,39",
    "description": "替换buff3"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "buff_4_up",
    "roiFront": "831,625,134,39",
    "roiBack": "831,625,134,39",
    "description": "替换buff4"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "buff_5_up",
    "roiFront": "1043,624,134,39",
    "roiBack": "1043,624,134,39",
    "description": "替换buff5"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "buff_1_box",
    "roiFront": "333,338,70,72",
    "roiBack": "333,338,70,72",
    "description": "上阵buff_1位置"
  },
  {
    "itemName": "buff_2_box",
    "roiFront": "877,220,59,62",
    "roiBack": "877,220,59,62",
    "description": "上阵buff_2位置"
  }
]